In order to get the append statement to work correctly,
للحصول على بيان إلحاق للعمل بشكل صحيح،
we need to rename the column in red_df,
نحن بحاجة إلى إعادة تسمية العمود red_df،
so that it matches the column name in the white_df.
بحيث يطابق اسم العمود في white_df.
To rename our columns in the previous lesson,
لإعادة تسمية الأعمدة في الدرس السابق، قمنا
we set df.columns to a new list.
بتعيين df.columns إلى قائمة جديدة.
Right now, we just need to change one of the column labels.
في الوقت الحالي، نحتاج فقط إلى تغيير أحد تسميات العمود.
If we try to do that by setting one value of
إذا حاولنا ذلك عن طريق تعيين قيمة واحدة من
df.columns by indexing it like this, we get an error.
df.columns عن طريق فهرستها على هذا النحو ، فسنحصل على خطأ.
Index does not support mutable operations.
لا يدعم الفهرس العمليات القابلة للتغيير.
This just means, that this column label array is something we can't modify.
هذا يعني، أن صفيف تسمية العمود هذا شيء لا يمكننا تعديله.
And since we can't modify it,
وبما أننا لا نستطيع تعديله،
we'd have to reassign the whole thing to a new list like this.
فسيتعين علينا إعادة تعيين الأمر بأكمله إلى قائمة جديدة كهذه.
Although this worked, this seems like a lot of work to change just one column name.
على الرغم من نجاح ذلك، يبدو أن هناك الكثير من العمل لتغيير اسم عمود واحد فقط.
We could do this better by using a method called rename.
يمكننا القيام بذلك بشكل أفضل باستخدام طريقة تسمى إعادة التسمية.
Look at the Stack Overflow page and try renaming
انظر إلى صفحة تجاوز سعة التكديس وجرب إعادة تسمية
the columns with this method in the Jupyter notebook in the next section.
الأعمدة بهذه الطريقة في تطبيق Jupyter notebook في الدرس التالي.